Now, we've heard a lot about you so far, Sakura-san.
Are you okay? Aren't you tired?
Oh, I'm totally fine.
But you know what, Yakan-kun, we've been talking all day too.
Aren't you tired?
It was fun, though.
Oh, I just got some really cute snacks.
Would you like to eat it with me? Here.
Oh, I like Halloween candy.
Yes! It's so cute!
I want some.
I love it!
I'll go trick-or-treating!
I'm Honoka Akimoto from Team Orca!
Yes, yes!
Yes!
I see.
I was just thinking how close you are to Yakkan.
You thought he was close?
Yeah. I was wondering how I knew all that.
You were?
It was you.
It was me.
I see.
It's Halloween.
Of course I'd say I'm a fan of Akimoto Honoka.
Aww... Ehhhhh...
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Ehhhhhh...
Hmmm...
Let's talk about the future of Team Orca from here!
Ooooooo...
Well, you know, there are only two months left in this year.
Well, we've got a lot of things on our schedule, don't we?
Well, Shachi will be going on a live house tour starting in December.
Yes!
Yes, from 2023 to 2024.
We'll be performing at Christmas and New Year's, and also near New Year's.
So we'll be performing 30 shows in 15 cities across the country.
That's a lot of excitement, isn't it?
Yes, we're going on a live house tour.
The title of the live tour has been announced, right?
That's right!
It's called "Live Spectacle: Life is Short, Let it Blossom.
Ohhh...
I'm so excited!
But "Live Spectacle" is also one of the points.
I think you can enjoy various kinds of orcas in this live performance.
Please come and see us!
And this live house tour is a tour with the full album!
The first full album this winter, right?
Since you became Wacky Records?
That's right. Yes, it is.
This is our first full-length album.
Yes, we're releasing it.
Yes!
Yes, we are in the middle of recording.
We have a lot of recording to do after this.
That's right.
There are so many different genres of songs.
The expression when you sing is different.
I'm going to sing with a smile on my face.
I'll go sing with a smile.
What about you?
I'm going to...
What's with your shoulder?
I'm singing like that.
You're probably right.
I'll probably end up like this live.
And I'm about to turn 26!
Happy birthday!
Yes!
Twenty-six!
That's a surprise, isn't it?
I didn't think I'd be able to do this activity until I'm 26.
That's what makes me happy.
I'm grateful to be in an environment where so many people support me even at my age, but I'm also very happy to be able to do this.
I will be celebrating my 26th birthday on November 19 at Nagoya Diamond Hall.
Please come and visit me there too!
Yay! Yay!
Please, please, please.
What are you doing?
I'm going to try something I've never tried before.
What do you call me?
I'm doing a live show.
In the live performance?
If it were you...
You sing the chorus with a voice like a punch in the face
Like a punch in the face.
You sing a lot of choruses, don't you?
That's right.
You do talk a lot, don't you, Mahou-san?
During live performances.
You do a lot of talking.
Talking?
Talking.
Lines?
Thank you for the lines.
I was thinking of doing a little bit of that.
I'm thinking of doing a little bit of everything.
I'm 26 years old and this is the first time I'm doing this.
You've got a lot on your plate, don't you?
That's right.
If I were to list all the parts I've done so far
There's no end to it.
Almost all the songs we've done so far.
Singles, title songs...You know, singles, title songs...
That's why there are dialogue parts in them.
I can't keep track.
I wonder how many lines there are.
I'm hoping that people will enjoy it.
It was fun.
How was it? I...
As a kettle?
I don't know...
I'm a kettlebug, too, so before I knew it...
I might have been a little too familiar.
You're right.
That's right.
You're always talking like a normal kettle of fish.
I'm not conscious of using honorifics.
I don't think we've ever spoken that close together.
So you were easy to talk to, is that right?
That's what I'm talking about.
Yay!
I think this is the first time you played the role of kettle boy.
How did you like it?
When I got the offer, I thought
I was almost crushed by the pressure of being the 4th kettle kettle
I was almost crushed by the pressure of being the 4th kettle.
But I decided to do my best in the role of the kettle
I tried my best to put my heart into the role of the kettle that I have been connecting with.
As a result, I was able to bring out my own version of the kettle.As a result of my efforts, I was able to create a kettle of my own.
I felt a sense of accomplishment.
Well, I hope I'll be invited again.
I'd like to use the 4th generation this time.
That's right.
I'm always looking forward to working with the fourth generation.
And so, up to this point, I've had the pleasure of working with
Honoka Akimoto, the team president
and Nao Sakura.
Bye bye!